A Guide to the Old Dominion University Photograph Collection 1930s-1990s
Special Collections, Perry Library, Old Dominion University
- 1980s
  - Psychology (Box-folder Box 93, Folder 13)
  - Public Safety (Box-folder Box 93, Folder 14)
  - Rathskeller (Box-folder Box 93, Folder 15)
  - Record Convention (Box-folder Box 93, Folder 16)
  - Registration (Box-folder Box 93, Folder 17)
  - Reich Room (Box-folder Box 94, Folder 1)
  - Research (Box-folder Box 94, Folder 2)
  - Royster Building (Box-folder Box 94, Folder 3)
  - ROTC (I) (Box-folder Box 94, Folder 4)
  - ROTC (II) (Box-folder Box 94, Folder 5)
  - Sailing (Box-folder Box 94, Folder 6)
  - Sciences (Box-folder Box 94, Folder 7)
  - Scottish Studies and Festival (Box-folder Box 94, Folder 8)
  - School Rings (Box-folder Box 94, Folder 9)
  - Snow (Box-folder Box 94, Folder 10)
  - Soccer Clinic (Box-folder Box 94, Folder 11)
  - Sociology (Box-folder Box 94, Folder 12)
  - Speakers and Guests (I) (Box-folder Box 94, Folder 13)
  - Speakers and Guests (II) (Box-folder Box 94, Folder 14)
  - Speech (Box-folder Box 95, Folder 1)
  - Sprit of Sports (Box-folder Box 95, Folder 2)
  - SSHP (Box-folder Box 95, Folder 3)
  - Staff A-I (Box-folder Box 95, Folder 4)
  - Staff J-R (Box-folder Box 95, Folder 5)
  - Student Health Center (Box-folder Box 95, Folder 6)
  - Student Life-On Campus (I) (Box-folder Box 95, Folder 7)
  - Student Life-On Campus (II) (Box-folder Box 95, Folder 8)
  - Student Life-On Campus (III) (Box-folder Box 95, Folder 9)
  - Student Life-On Campus (IV) (Box-folder Box 95, Folder 10)
  - Student Life-In Class (Box-folder Box 96, Folder 1)
  - Student Life-Preview (Box-folder Box 96, Folder 2)
  - Student Portraits (Box-folder Box 96, Folder 3)
  - Student Presidents (Box-folder Box 96, Folder 4)
  - Student Services (Box-folder Box 96, Folder 5)
  - Students-Handicapped (Box-folder Box 96, Folder 6)
  - Summer of 1985 (Box-folder Box 96, Folder 7)
  - Summer Workshop in the Arts (Box-folder Box 96, Folder 8)
  - Super Dance (Box-folder Box 96, Folder 9)
  - Taft Institutes (Box-folder Box 96, Folder 10)
  - Television Center (Box-folder Box 96, Folder 11)
  - Theater (I) (Box-folder Box 96, Folder 12)
  - Theater (II) (Box-folder Box 96, Folder 13)
  - Tournament of Terminals (Box-folder Box 97, Folder 1)
  - United Way (Box-folder Box 97, Folder 2)
  - University Medal (Box-folder Box 97, Folder 3)
  - UN Conference (Box-folder Box 97, Folder 4)
  - Urban Services Center (Box-folder Box 97, Folder 5)
  - Vo-Tech/Industrial Arts (Box-folder Box 97, Folder 6)
  - Visiting Speakers (Box-folder Box 97, Folder 7)
  - Weather Center (Box-folder Box 97, Folder 8)
  - Webb Center (Box-folder Box 97, Folder 9)
  - Weight/Nautilus Room (Box-folder Box 97, Folder 10)
  - Wild Shots (Box-folder Box 97, Folder 11)
  - WODU (Box-folder Box 97, Folder 12)
  - Women's Basketball (Box-folder Box 97, Folder 13)
  - Women's Center (Box-folder Box 97, Folder 14)
  - Woodworking (Box-folder Box 97, Folder 15)
  - Workshops, Conferences, Seminars (Box-folder Box 97, Folder 16)
  - World Trade Center (Norfolk) (Box-folder Box 97, Folder 17)
  - Wrestling (Box-folder Box 97, Folder 18)
  - Writing Center (Box-folder Box 97, Folder 19)
  - Zuni Pine Barren (Box-folder Box 97, Folder 20)
- 1990s
  - Campus-Academic Advising (Box-folder Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Campus-Admissions (Box-folder Box 98, Folder 2)
  - Campus-African-American Center (Box-folder Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Campus-Architectural Elements (Box-folder Box 98, Folder 4)
  - Campus-Board of Visitors (Box-folder Box 98, Folder 5)
  - Campus-Bookstore (Box-folder Box 98, Folder 6)
  - Campus-Bus Tour (Box-folder Box 98, Folder 7)
  - Campus-Improvement and Construction (I) (Box-folder Box 98, Folder 8)
  - Campus-Improvement and Construction (II) (Box-folder Box 98, Folder 9)
  - Campus-Career Advantage Program (Box-folder Box 98, Folder 10)
  - Campus-Child Study/Special Education (Box-folder Box 99, Folder 1)
  - Campus-Counseling Center (Box-folder Box 99, Folder 2)
  - Campus-Disabled Services (Box-folder Box 99, Folder 3)
  - Campus-Dormitories (Box-folder Box 99, Folder 4)
  - Campus-Dragas International Center (Box-folder Box 99, Folder 5)
  - Campus-Grounds and Buildings-Exteriors (I) (Box-folder Box 99, Folder 6)
  - Campus-Grounds and Buildings-Exteriors (II) (Box-folder Box 99, Folder 7)
  - Campus-Grounds and Buildings-Exteriors (III) (Box-folder Box 99, Folder 8)
  - Campus-Grounds and Buildings-Exteriors (IV) (Box-folder Box 99, Folder 9)
  - Campus-Grounds and Buildings-Foreman Field (Box-folder Box 99, Folder 10)
  - Campus-Grounds and Buildings-Interiors (Box-folder Box 99, Folder 11)
  - Campus-Grounds and Buildings-Library (Box-folder Box 99, Folder 12)
  - Campus-Grounds and Buildings-Rollins Hall (Box-folder Box 100, Folder 1)
  - Campus-Grounds and Buildings-The University Wall (Box-folder Box 100, Folder 2)
  - Campus-Physical Plant (Box-folder Box 100, Folder 3)
  - Campus-Registrar (Box-folder Box 100, Folder 4)
  - Campus-Student Financial Aid (Box-folder Box 100, Folder 5)
  - Campus-Women's Center (Box-folder Box 100, Folder 6)
  - College of Arts and Letters (Box-folder Box 100, Folder 7)
  - College of Arts and Letters-Art (Box-folder Box 100, Folder 8)
  - College of Arts and Letters-Ballet (Box-folder Box 100, Folder 9)
  - College of Arts and Letters-Dance (Box-folder Box 100, Folder 10)
  - College of Arts and Letters-English (Box-folder Box 101, Folder 1)
  - College of Arts and Letters-English Language Center (Box-folder Box 101, Folder 2)
  - College of Arts and Letters-Foreign Languages and Literature (Box-folder Box 101, Folder 3)
  - College of Arts and Letters-Hampton Roads School for the Arts (Box-folder Box 101, Folder 4)
  - College of Arts and Letters-History (Box-folder Box 101, Folder 5)
  - College of Arts and Letters-Interdisciplinary Studies (Box-folder Box 101, Folder 6)
  - College of Arts and Letters-Institute of Humanities (Box-folder Box 101, Folder 7)
  - College of Arts and Letters-Liberal Arts/Continuing Education (Box-folder Box 101, Folder 8)
  - College of Arts and Letters-Model U.N. (Box-folder Box 101, Folder 9)
  - College of Arts and Letters-Music (I) (Box-folder Box 101, Folder 10)
  - College of Arts and Letters-Music (II) (Box-folder Box 101, Folder 11)
  - College of Arts and Letters-Political Science and Geography (Box-folder Box 102, Folder 1)
  - College of Arts and Letters-Sociology and Criminal Justice (Box-folder Box 102, Folder 2)
  - College of Arts and Letters-Speech, Communication, and Theater Arts (Box-folder Box 102, Folder 3)
  - College of Arts and Letters-Speech Department Faculty (Box-folder Box 102, Folder 4)
  - College of Arts and Letters-Women's Studies (Box-folder Box 102, Folder 5)
  - College of Business and Public Administration (Box-folder Box 102, Folder 6)
  - College of Business and Public Administration-Accounting (Box-folder Box 102, Folder 7)
  - College of Business and Public Administration-Economics Department (Box-folder Box 102, Folder 8)
  - College of Business and Public Administration-International Maritime, Ports and Logistics Management Institute (Box-folder Box 102, Folder 9)
  - College of Education (Box-folder Box 102, Folder 10)
  - College of Education-Elderhostel (Box-folder Box 102, Folder 11)
  - College of Engineering and Technology (Box-folder Box 102, Folder 12)
  - College of Engineering and Technology-Aerospace Engineering (Box-folder Box 102, Folder 13)
  - College of Engineering and Technology-Civil Engineering (Box-folder Box 102, Folder 14)
  - College of Engineering and Technology-Commonwealth Graduate Engineering Program (Box-folder Box 102, Folder 15)
  - College of Engineering and Technology-Electrical and Computer Engineering (Box-folder Box 102, Folder 16)
  - College of Engineering and Technology-Engineering Management (Box-folder Box 102, Folder 17)
  - College of Engineering and Technology-Engineering Technology (Box-folder Box 103, Folder 1)
  - College of Engineering and Technology-Mechanical Engineering (Box-folder Box 103, Folder 2)
  - College of Engineering and Technology-Technology Applications Center (Box-folder Box 103, Folder 3)
  - College of Health Sciences-Community Health Professions and Physical Therapy (Box-folder Box 103, Folder 4)
  - College of Health Sciences-Dental Hygiene and Assisting (Box-folder Box 103, Folder 5)
  - College of Health Sciences-Health P.E. and Recreation (Box-folder Box 103, Folder 6)
  - College of Health Sciences-Medical Laboratory Sciences (Box-folder Box 103, Folder 7)
  - College of Health Sciences-School of Nursing (Box-folder Box 103, Folder 8)
  - College of Sciences (Box-folder Box 103, Folder 9)
  - College of Sciences-Applied Marine Research Lab (Box-folder Box 103, Folder 10)
  - College of Sciences-Biological Sciences (Box-folder Box 103, Folder 11)
  - College of Sciences-Biomedical Sciences (Box-folder Box 103, Folder 12)
  - College of Sciences-Chemistry and Biochemistry (Box-folder Box 103, Folder 13)
  - College of Sciences-Computer Science (Box-folder Box 103, Folder 14)
  - College of Sciences-Ecological Sciences (Box-folder Box 104, Folder 1)
  - College of Sciences-Geological Sciences (Box-folder Box 104, Folder 2)
  - College of Sciences-Mathematics and Statistics (Box-folder Box 104, Folder 3)
  - College of Sciences-Oceanography (I) (Box-folder Box 104, Folder 4)
  - College of Sciences-Oceanography (II) (Box-folder Box 104, Folder 5)
  - College of Sciences-Physics (Box-folder Box 104, Folder 6)
  - College of Sciences-Psychology (Box-folder Box 104, Folder 7)
  - Events-Awards (Box-folder Box 104, Folder 8)
  - Events-Awards: Students (Box-folder Box 104, Folder 9)
  - Events-Big Blue Bash (Box-folder Box 104, Folder 10)
  - Events-Black History Month (Box-folder Box 104, Folder 11)
  - Events-Christmas Party (Box-folder Box 104, Folder 12)
  - Events-Concert Series (Box-folder Box 104, Folder 13)
  - Events-Danceathon (Box-folder Box 104, Folder 14)
  - Events-Diehn Concert Series (Box-folder Box 104, Folder 15)
  - Events-Famous People (I) (Box-folder Box 105, Folder 1)
  - Events-Famous People (II) (Box-folder Box 105, Folder 2)
  - Events-Famous People (III) (Box-folder Box 105, Folder 3)
  - Events-Famous People (IV) (Box-folder Box 105, Folder 4)
  - Events-Famous People (V) (Box-folder Box 105, Folder 5)
  - Events-Famous People (VI) (Box-folder Box 105, Folder 6)
  - Events-Famous People (VII) (Box-folder Box 105, Folder 7)
  - Events-Famous People (VIII) (Box-folder Box 106, Folder 1)
  - Events-Famous People (IX) (Box-folder Box 106, Folder 2)
  - Events-First African-American Graduates (Box-folder Box 106, Folder 3)
  - Events-Glennan Lecture Series (Box-folder Box 106, Folder 4)
  - Events-Habitat for Humanity (Box-folder Box 106, Folder 5)
  - Events-Honoring Webb (Box-folder Box 106, Folder 6)
  - Events-Job Fair (Box-folder Box 106, Folder 7)
  - Events-Literary Festival (Box-folder Box 106, Folder 8)
  - Events-Madrigal Dinner (Box-folder Box 106, Folder 9)
  - Events-Main Street (Box-folder Box 106, Folder 10)
  - Events-Miscellaneous (Box-folder Box 106, Folder 11)
  - Events-Parent's Weekend (Box-folder Box 107, Folder 1)
  - Events-Philanthropy (Box-folder Box 107, Folder 2)
  - Events-President's Lecture Series (Box-folder Box 107, Folder 3)
  - Events-Spring Dance and Supper (Box-folder Box 107, Folder 4)
  - Events-University Medal (Box-folder Box 107, Folder 5)
  - Events-Waldo Lecture Series (Box-folder Box 107, Folder 6)
  - International Programs (Box-folder Box 107, Folder 7)
  - International Programs-Cultural (Box-folder Box 107, Folder 8)
  - International Programs-International Studies (I) (Box-folder Box 107, Folder 9)
  - International Programs-International Studies (II) (Box-folder Box 107, Folder 10)
  - International Programs-World Fest (Box-folder Box 107, Folder 11)
  - Military-Activities (Box-folder Box 107, Folder 12)
  - Military-Career Transitions (Box-folder Box 107, Folder 13)
  - Military-Military Science (I) (Box-folder Box 108, Folder 1)
  - Military-Military Science (II) (Box-folder Box 108, Folder 2)
  - Military-Military Science (III) (Box-folder Box 108, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous-AA-EEO (Box-folder Box 108, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous-Academic Affairs (Box-folder Box 108, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous-Academic Honors (Box-folder Box 108, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous-Academic Television Services (Box-folder Box 108, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous-Basketball (Box-folder Box 108, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous-Community Outreach Program (Box-folder Box 108, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous-Development (Box-folder Box 108, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous-Faculty and Staff (Box-folder Box 108, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous-Grounds and Buildings (Box-folder Box 108, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous-Guest Speakers and Performers (I) (Box-folder Box 109, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous-Guest Speakers and Performers (II) (Box-folder Box 109, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous-Guest Speakers and Performers (III) (Box-folder Box 109, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous-Guest Speakers and Performers (IV) (Box-folder Box 109, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous-Guest Speakers and Performers (V) (Box-folder Box 109, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous-Hourly and Classified Employee Association (HACE) (Box-folder Box 109, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous-Industrial Programs (Box-folder Box 109, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous-Journal and Guide Photos (Box-folder Box 109, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous (I) (Box-folder Box 109, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous (II) (Box-folder Box 109, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous (III) (Box-folder Box 109, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous (IV) (Box-folder Box 109, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous (V) (Box-folder Box 109, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous (VI) (Box-folder Box 110, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous (VII) (Box-folder Box 110, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous (VIII) (Box-folder Box 110, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous (IX) (Box-folder Box 110, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous (X) (Box-folder Box 110, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous (XI) (Box-folder Box 110, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous (XII) (Box-folder Box 110, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous (XIII) (Box-folder Box 110, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous-Preview (I) (Box-folder Box 110, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous-Preview (II) (Box-folder Box 110, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous-Provost (I) (Box-folder Box 111, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous-Provost (II) (Box-folder Box 111, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous-Provost (III) (Box-folder Box 111, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous-Public Safety (Box-folder Box 111, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous-Samantha Silvia (Box-folder Box 111, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous-Summer Programs-Lambert's Point (Box-folder Box 111, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous-Teletechnet (Box-folder Box 111, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous-Virginia Assistive Technical Service (Box-folder Box 111, Folder 8)
  - Off Campus-Aerial Photographs (Box-folder Box 111, Folder 9)
  - Off Campus-Norfolk (Box-folder Box 111, Folder 10)
  - Off Campus-Surrounding Areas (Box-folder Box 111, Folder 11)
  - Off Campus-Waterside/Harborfest (Box-folder Box 111, Folder 12)
  - Off Campus Centers-CARSM-Center for Advanced Ship Repair and Maintenance (Box-folder Box 111, Folder 13)
  - Off Campus Centers-ODU/NSU Virginia Beach Center (Box-folder Box 111, Folder 14)
  - Off Campus Centers-Peninsula (Box-folder Box 111, Folder 15)
  - Off Campus Centers-Shipyard (Box-folder Box 111, Folder 16)
  - Off Campus Centers-Virginia Beach (Box-folder Box 111, Folder 17)
  - Office of the President (I) (Box-folder Box 112, Folder 1)
  - Office of the President (II) (Box-folder Box 112, Folder 2)
  - Office of the President (III) (Box-folder Box 112, Folder 3)
  - Office of the President (IV) (Box-folder Box 112, Folder 4)
  - Office of the President (V) (Box-folder Box 112, Folder 5)
  - Office of the President (VI) (Box-folder Box 112, Folder 6)
  - Office of the President (VII) (Box-folder Box 112, Folder 7)
  - Office of the President (VIII) (Box-folder Box 112, Folder 8)
  - Office of the President (IX) (Box-folder Box 112, Folder 9)
  - Office of the President (X) (Box-folder Box 112, Folder 10)
  - Office of the President (XI) (Box-folder Box 112, Folder 11)
  - Resident Life (I) (Box-folder Box 113, Folder 1)
  - Resident Life (II) (Box-folder Box 113, Folder 2)
  - Resident Life (III) (Box-folder Box 113, Folder 3)
  - Resident Life (IV) (Box-folder Box 113, Folder 4)
  - Resident Life (V) (Box-folder Box 113, Folder 5)
  - Resident Life (VI) (Box-folder Box 113, Folder 6)
  - Resident Life (VII) (Box-folder Box 113, Folder 7)
  - Resident Life (VIII) (Box-folder Box 113, Folder 8)
  - Resident Life (IX) (Box-folder Box 113, Folder 9)
  - Resident Life (X) (Box-folder Box 113, Folder 10)
  - Resident Life (XI) (Box-folder Box 113, Folder 11)
  - Resident Life (XII) (Box-folder Box 113, Folder 12)
  - Resident Life (XIII) (Box-folder Box 114, Folder 1)
  - Resident Life (XIV) (Box-folder Box 114, Folder 2)
  - Resident Life (VI) (Box-folder Box 114, Folder 3)
  - Student Life-Alumni Relations (I) (Box-folder Box 114, Folder 4)
  - Student Life-Alumni Relations (II) (Box-folder Box 114, Folder 5)
  - Student Life-Alumni Relations (III) (Box-folder Box 114, Folder 6)
  - Student Life-Alumni Relations (IV) (Box-folder Box 114, Folder 7)
  - Student Life-Alumni Relations (V) (Box-folder Box 114, Folder 8)
  - Student Life-Alumni Relations (VI) (Box-folder Box 114, Folder 9)
  - Student Life-Alumni Relations (VII) (Box-folder Box 114, Folder 10)
  - Student Life-Class-Indoors (I) (Box-folder Box 114, Folder 11)
  - Student Life-Class-Indoors (II) (Box-folder Box 114, Folder 12)
  - Student Life-Class-Indoors (III) (Box-folder Box 115, Folder 1)
  - Student Life-Class-Indoors (IV) (Box-folder Box 115, Folder 2)
  - Student Life-Class-Indoors (V) (Box-folder Box 115, Folder 3)
  - Student Life-Class-Labs (I) (Box-folder Box 115, Folder 4)
  - Student Life-Class-Labs (II) (Box-folder Box 115, Folder 5)
  - Student Life-Class-Labs (III) (Box-folder Box 115, Folder 6)
  - Student Life-Class-Labs (IV) (Box-folder Box 115, Folder 7)
  - Student Life-Class-Labs (V) (Box-folder Box 115, Folder 8)
  - Student Life-Class-Outdoors (Box-folder Box 115, Folder 9)
  - Student Life-Commencement (I) (Box-folder Box 116, Folder 1)
  - Student Life-Commencement (II) (Box-folder Box 116, Folder 2)
  - Student Life-Commencement (III) (Box-folder Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Student Life-Commencement (IV) (Box-folder Box 116, Folder 4)
  - Student Life-Commencement (V) (Box-folder Box 116, Folder 5)
  - Student Life-Commencement (VI) (Box-folder Box 116, Folder 6)
  - Student Life-Commencement (VII) (Box-folder Box 116, Folder 7)
  - Student Life-Commencement (VIII) (Box-folder Box 116, Folder 8)
  - Student Life-Commencement (IX) (Box-folder Box 116, Folder 9)
  - Student Life-Greeks (Box-folder Box 116, Folder 10)
  - Student Life-Group Shots-Large Groups (I) (Box-folder Box 117, Folder 1)
  - Student Life-Group Shots-Large Groups (II) (Box-folder Box 117, Folder 2)
  - Student Life-Group Shots-Small Groups (I) (Box-folder Box 117, Folder 3)
  - Student Life-Group Shots-Large Groups (II) (Box-folder Box 117, Folder 4)
  - Student Life-Group Shots-Large Groups (III) (Box-folder Box 117, Folder 5)
  - Student Life-Group Shots-Large Groups (IV) (Box-folder Box 117, Folder 6)
  - Student Life-Group Shots-Large Groups (V) (Box-folder Box 117, Folder 7)
  - Student Life-Group Shots-Large Groups (VI) (Box-folder Box 117, Folder 8)
  - Student Life-Group Shots-Large Groups (VII) (Box-folder Box 117, Folder 9)
  - Student Life-Group Shots-Large Groups (VIII) (Box-folder Box 117, Folder 10)
  - Student Life-Individuals (I) (Box-folder Box 118, Folder 1)
  - Student Life-Individuals (II) (Box-folder Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Student Life-Minorities (Box-folder Box 118, Folder 3)
  - Student Life-Phi Kappa Phi Honors (Box-folder Box 118, Folder 4)
  - Student Life-Recreational Activities (I) (Box-folder Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Student Life-Recreational Activities (II) (Box-folder Box 118, Folder 6)
  - Student Life-Recreational Activities (III) (Box-folder Box 118, Folder 7)
  - Student Life-Student Ambassadors (Box-folder Box 118, Folder 8)
  - Student Life-Student Services (Box-folder Box 118, Folder 9)
  - Student Life-Studying (I) (Box-folder Box 118, Folder 10)
  - Student Life-Studying (II) (Box-folder Box 118, Folder 11)
  - Student Life-Various Groups (I) (Box-folder Box 119, Folder 1)
  - Student Life-Various Groups (II) (Box-folder Box 119, Folder 2)
  - Student Life-Various Groups (III) (Box-folder Box 119, Folder 3)
  - Student Life-Various Groups (IV) (Box-folder Box 119, Folder 4)
  - Student Life-Various Groups (V) (Box-folder Box 119, Folder 5)
  - Student Life-Various Groups (VI) (Box-folder Box 119, Folder 6)
  - Sports-Baseball (Box-folder Box 119, Folder 7)
  - Sports-Big Blue Mascot (Box-folder Box 119, Folder 8)
  - Sports-Cheerleaders (Box-folder Box 119, Folder 9)
  - Sports-Field Hockey (Box-folder Box 119, Folder 10)
  - Sports-La Crosse (Box-folder Box 119, Folder 11)
  - Sports-Martial Arts (Box-folder Box 119, Folder 12)
  - Sports-Men's Basketball (I) (Box-folder Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Sports-Men's Basketball (II) (Box-folder Box 120, Folder 2)
  - Sports-Men's Cross-Country (Box-folder Box 120, Folder 3)
  - Sports-Men's Soccer (Box-folder Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Sports-Men's Tennis (Box-folder Box 120, Folder 5)
  - Sports-Rowing (Box-folder Box 120, Folder 6)
  - Sports-Rugby (Box-folder Box 120, Folder 7)
  - Sports-Sailing (Box-folder Box 120, Folder 8)
  - Sports-Sports Medicine (Box-folder Box 120, Folder 9)
  - Sports-Swimming (Box-folder Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Sports-Women's Basketball (I) (Box-folder Box 120, Folder 11)
  - Sports-Women's Basketball (II) (Box-folder Box 120, Folder 12)
  - Sports-Women's Cross Country (Box-folder Box 120, Folder 13)
  - Sports-Wrestling (Box-folder Box 120, Folder 14)